

Kollegievej 6, st., -104, 9000 Aalborg, Denmark (Willing to move)

□ (+45) 29405039 | ☑ robinbjerring@gmail.com | 🏔 www.robinbjerring.com | 🛅 robinwoelkbjerring

## Summary\_

Empathetic IT Design graduate skilled in game design, level design, project management, agile development, user experience and leadership. Love solving problems and creating new and compelling experiences. Have made games, created a network for blockchain enthusiasts, owned an online comic book store and been a presenter as well as music planner for a festival.

### Skills\_

Design Level design, Game Design, Design document, Photoshop, Gamification, Rapid prototyping, Excel for game stat management

Management Leadership, Agile Project Management, SCRUM, Kanban, Trello, Conflict management.

Users User testing, UX, analysis of user data.

**Tech** Unity Engine, Sourcetree user, C# (currently learning), system administration.

Languages Danish (Native), English (Professional capacity), Norwegian Bokmål (read/understand), Swedish (read/understand).

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

**DADIU** Aalborg, Denmark

LEAD GAME DESIGNER, INTERNSHIP

- Lead Game Designer on iOS and Android game developed in Unity. Did game-, level- and UX design.
- Lead technical production. Communicated and coordinated with 17 students.
- · Created test builds for quality assurance/UX testers.
- · Grade: A (ECTS).

Heroshop.dk Birkerød

OWNER OF ONLINE COMIC BOOK STORE

• Used PrestaShop to build the online comic book store and sell comic books. · Created ads on Facebook and did all social media marketing.

**Farum Municipality** Farum, Denmark

IT SUPPORT INTERN Jan. 2017 - Mar. 2017

- Upgraded hardware of laptop and desktop PC's also installed OS and software.
- Did off-site administration of printers.
- · Was introduced to VMware server administration.

**Gjensidige** Copenhagen, Denmark

BOOKER OF MEETINGS

· Did B2B and B2C contact.

· Set up meetings with potential customers.

Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2016

Aug. 2018 - Dec. 2018

Sep. 2016 - Apr. 2018

### Honors & Awards

Winner, Nordic Game Jam - Board Game Track (Jury & Public Choice Awards) 2016

Copenhagen, DK

Article, Apple included DADIU game Night Painter game in Made in Denmark list

Apple, DK

## **Education**

**Aalborg University** Aalborg, Denmark

M.Sc. IT IN INTERACTIVE DIGITAL MEDIA

Sep. 2017 - Jun. 2019

· It design, agile project management, concept development, digital narratology, game design, gamification, prototyping.

**Aalborg University** B.A. IN COMMUNICATION & DIGITAL MEDIA

Aalborg, Denmark

Sep. 2012 - Jun. 2015

• Educated in communication, media production, communication strategy, aesthetics.

AUGUST 6, 2019 ROBIN WOELK BJERRING · RESUME

## **Extracurricular Activity**

**Aalborg University** Aalborg, Denmark

**VOLUNTEER GUEST LECTURER** Oct. 2017

- Did lectures on Bitcoin and blockchain technology for peers.
- Created workshop where students had to come up with possible use cases for blockchain.

#### **Aalborg Blockchain Network**

Aalborg, Denmark Nov. 2017 - PRESENT

FOUNDER

- · Founder of network for blockchain enthusiasts.
- · Have done talks on various applications for blockchain technology.

**Freedom Festival Aalborg** 

VOLUNTEER MUSIC PLANNER & PRESENTER

Jun. 2018 - Sep. 2018

- Contacted all bands and planned the festival music program. Handled 12 bands over two days.
- · Was the presenter for the festival. Stood on the scene and bit everyone welcome and introduced every band throughout the days.

# **University Projects**

### When music and difficulty meet:

### How music affects perception of a video game's difficulty

**Aalborg** Jun. 2019

• Flow theory, SAM tests, psychophysiological data and user interviews.

- · Analyses whether the presence of music affects the user's perception of a game's difficulty.
- · Grade ECTS: B

### Computer Games at the National Academy of Digital Interactive Entertainment (DADIU)

Aalborg Dec. 2018

SEMESTER EXAM ASSIGNMENT

· Exam in my game design and leadership work at DADIU as well as analytical reflections on the semester.

· Grade ECTS: A

### "Well Played" - A Winning Strategy for eSport as a Business Model

Aalborg

· Investigates how multiplayer games can elevate eSport as a business model. Analyses loot boxes, battle passes and more.

Jun. 2018

- · Grade ECTS: B

### **The Pursuit of Intelligent Computer Games**

Aalborg

SEMESTER PROJECT

Dec. 2017

- · Discusses current and future applications for self-learning algorithms (machine learning / AI) in video games.
- · Grade ECTS: B